In the previous exercise we saw the use of tabbed navigation and tabs and tab page.
在之前的练习中，我们了解了选项卡导航、选项卡、选项卡页的用法
Now we're going to convert those tabs into
接下来，我们将选项卡转变为
an accordion using the collapse class that we just learned about.
一个手风琴，使用刚刚学习的折叠类
In addition, we're going to make use of the scroll spy and
此外，我们将要利用刚学到的滚动监听(Scrollspy)和
affix class that we just learned in order to introduce
附加导航 (Affix) 类
some side navigation to our about start HTML pitch.
以便引入侧边导航栏到我们的 about.html 页面
Getting back to our web page,
回到我们的网页
let's do a little bit of housekeeping on this web page and creat space so
让我们在页面上做一点清理工作 留出一些空间
that we can introduce the sidebar using the scroll spy and affix later on.
以便引入滚动监听和附加导航来实现的侧边导航栏
We will also convert the tabs and the tab navigation into accordion now.
我们还会把选项卡和选项卡导航转变为手风琴
So going through this webpage, you notice that the second and
过一遍这个页面，你会发现第二行和
the third rows have some empty space on the right side.
第三行的右边有一些空白区域
So we're gonna delete that empty space and
我们将要移除这些空白区域
let these two rows stretch completely the entire screen.
让这两行完全扩展到整个屏幕
Now, the first row, I'm gonna cut down the size a little bit, because
而对于第一行，我要缩减一点点大小，因为
when we push the content to the left here in order to accommodate the skull spy,
当我们把内容往左边推，以便在这放入滚动监听插件时
some of these content will look a little squished on the left side.
左边的一些内容会看起来有点挤压
So let's do that housekeeping and then we'll come back and look at the webpage
所以，在我们去实现手风琴效果之前
before we move on to working on introducing the Accordion.
让我们做一下清理工作，然后回头看看这网页
Going to your web page content, I am now going to adjust
打开你的页面代码，我现在打算去调整
the columns specifications for the first row.
第一行中的列相关的排版定义
Previously we were using column sm-8.
之前我们使用了 col-sm-8
I'm going to reduce that to column SM6, but for large screens
我打算把该列缩减到 col-sm-6，但对于大屏幕
Its fine to keep the eight columns for the first part of the content.
我们可以继续为第一行的第一部分保留 8 列
So let me update the column classes here I
所以让我来更新一下这里的列排版类
have updated the column classes to column SM6 and column LG8 so for
我已经在这更新列排版类为 col-sm-6 和 col-lg-8
the mediums I screened also The six will still apply.
所以，对于中等屏幕大小也会应用 6 列
The other part of this row which contains the panel,
在本行中包含面板的那部分
I have adjusted the column classes appropriately.
我已经相应地调整了列排版类
So I have used column sm-6 and column lg-4 for this.
我在这使用了 col-sm-6 和 col-lg-4
The remaining two rows I'm going to adjust the column class so
对于余下的两行，我打算调整列排版类
that is occupies the entire 12 columns for the content,
以使其内容占据整个 12 列
which also means that I need to remove the div which was reserved for
也就是说我需要移去右边那个
the empty space on the right side.
保留空白区域的 div
For the second column, I have adjusted so that it occupies the entire 12 rows,
对于第二行，我调整了使其占据整个 12 列
and then I have removed the second div which was in this particular row.
然后移除了本行中的第二个 div
Same thing for the third row also.
对于第三行也做同样的处理
After making the changes, looking at the state of the web page
做完这些改变之后，看看当前页面的状态
you notice that the columns have been adjusted accordingly, the second and
你会发现这些列被相应地做了调整
the third row now occupy the entire 12 columns here.
第二行和第三行则占据了整个 12 列
Now we are going to later on squish these to the left by introducing a relational
现在，随后我们打算把这些内容压到左边
road to nest this content so that we will create enough space on
通过引入额外的行去包裹这些内容 以便在右边
the right side to introduce this scroll spy and the effects.
创建足够的空间来引入滚动监听和附加导航
In our next step, we're going to go to these tabs that we created for
下一步，我们打算把这些为公司领导人创建的
the corporate leadership and then replace that with an accordion.
选项卡替换成手风琴效果
We're going to make use of the collapse class that we have learned earlier
我们打算利用之前学到的折叠类
together with the panel that we have
以及上一节课看到的面板
seen in the previous module and the panel group, that is a group of panels.
和面板组，也就是一组面板
And then we are gonna make use of that to design the accordion for
然后我们打算利用这些知识去
the different corporate leadership, here.
为公司领导人设计手风琴效果
So, all these tabs will be turned into accordions using these classes.
因此，所有这些选项卡将会使用这些类去转变成手风琴
Going back to the code,
回到代码部分
I am now going to remove the tab navigation that I have introduced earlier.
我现在要去删除之前引入的选项卡导航
So the ul that we introduced for the tab navigation will be completely removed, and
所以，这些为选项卡导航引入的 ul 会被完全删除
then I will start turning each of those tab panes into panels and
然后，我会把每个选项页转变成面板
enclose them inside a panel group.
并嵌入到面板组中去
And then apply the appropriate collapse classes to turn that into an accordion.
然后相应地添加折叠类，使其变成手风琴
I have now deleted the tabbed navigation.
我现在已经删除了选项卡导航
Now I'm going to take this div and then turn that into a panel group first.
首先，我打算把这个 div 转变成 panel-group
So I have now replaced the tab content with a div with the class panel group.
所以，我现在用带有 panel-group 类的 div 替换掉 tab-content 类
So anything inside, all the panels inside will now form a group of panels and
所有里面的面板将组成一组面板
such that the spacing between them is adjusted appropriately.
这样，它们之间的空间就会做相应的调整
And we can then apply the accordion to this group of panels here.
然后，我们就可以为这组面板实现手风琴效果
In the next step, I'm going to replace this tab here and turn that into a panel,
在下一步，我将要替换掉这个 tabpanel 并把它改成一个 panel
and then I'll move the name of the CEO into the panel heading.
然后把 CEO 的名字移到 panel-heading 中
Then the panel content, the P that we had where we described
而对于内容，这个用于描述内容的段落 P
the content, will be moved into a panel body.
将会被移到一个 panel-body 里
I have first introduced that panel there and
我首先在这引入了 panel
then the panel heading, for the very first panel.
然后是第一个 panel 的 panel-heading
So this first panel will contain the details about our CEO.
所以，第一个面板将包含关于我们 CEO 的详细描述
So, in this panel, you can notice that I have the div for the panel and
在这个面板中，你会发现我为这个面板使用了一个 div
then after that, I have introduced the inner div for the panel heading.
并在随后，为 panel-heading 使用了一个内嵌的 div
So this is the typical structure that we have seen for
所以，这是我们之前所见到的
panels, where panel headings earlier.
典型的 panel panel-heading 结构
Now inside that, I am using the h3 class, which I have turned into a panel title.
而在这里面，我使用了 h3 类，并把它转为 panel-title
So this contains the name of the Cu.
所以，这里包含了 CEO 的名字
Now in order to turn this panel title in to a control for
为了把这个 panel-title 转变为对手风琴的控制
the accordion class so that when you click on the link there or
以便当你点击这个链接或者说 CEO 名字时
the name of the CEO there, then the panel will open and
对应的面板会打开或关闭
close so the collapse feature will be introduced there.
也就是说折叠功能会在这里引入
For that, I am introducing an A tag here.
为此，我在这引入了一个 A 标签
Now inside the A tag, I am applying the data toggle as collapse and
在 A 标签里，我应用了 data-toggle="collapse"
the data-parent, I am pointing to the accordion,
而 data-parent 则指向 #accordion (手风琴)
which I have introduced earlier, the panel group whose ID is accordion.
也就是我之前引入的 panel-group 的 ID 就叫 accordion
So that's the data parent for it.
这就是 data-parent 的值
And so this completes the setting up of the panel heading.
目前就完成了 panel-heading 的设置
Now let's go into the panel content itself, the panel body.
现在，让我们来设置面板内容本身，也就是 panel-body
And then make the changes there, and
然后在这进行修改
then go back and look at what happened to the web page design.
再回过头来看看网页长什么样
In the next step I have introduced another dev there
在下一步中，我在这引入了另一个 div
with the class panel collapse and collapse and in.
并设置了  class="panel-collapse collapse in"
Which means that this particular panel will be opened
这表示当页面最初加载时
when the webpage is first rendered.
本面板为打开状态
So whatever content is there inside will be displayed on the web page
面板里的任何内容都会
when you first visit the web page.
在你第一次打开网页时显示出来
This panel can be turned on and off by using the collapse class there.
这个面板 在你使用 collapse 类后可以切换为展开或折叠状态
After making these changes, let's go back and look at our webpage.
做完这些改动后
Taking a look at out webpage you can now see that the content
现在来看看我们的网页 你可以看到这里的内容
is enclosed inside a panel here.
被包含在一个面板里
Now if you click on the panel heading here
现在，如果你在面板标题 (panel-heading) 上单击
the content will, can be collapsed and then shown again.
这里的内容将会折叠，然后再次展开
So this is the collapse class coming into action here.
所以折叠类在这起作用了
Now we're going to apply the same for
现在，我们将要把同样的修改
the remaining three corporate leaders in there.
应用到余下的三个公司领导人那
And then come back and look at the result on the page.
然后，再回头看看网页的效果
I have now done the same change to the second corporate
我现在已经把同样的修改应用到了第二个公司领导人信息那
leader's information there, and I have applied the panel and
然后就像以前一样应用修改到 panel 和 panel-heading
the panel heading just like I did before, and the panel title and the A role there.
以及 panel-title 和 A role
Now coming down to the panel body itself,
下面来到 panel-body 本身
notice that here I have applied the classes panel collapse, collapse here.
请注意我在这里设置了 class="panel-collapse collapse"
I then applied the in class here which means that this particular panel I
我并没有在这添加 in 类 也就是说对于本面板
want it to start out in the closed mode so that means that it's not gonna be showed.
我希望它一开始就折叠状态的 也就意味着并不会显示出来
A little bit close in this when the page is first visited.
在网页第一次打开时会呈关闭状态
So going back and looking at the webpage again,
让我们再回到网页中来
we'll notice that we've introduced the second panel into the group there.
我们将发现已经引入了第二个面板到面板组中了
Going back to our webpage you can now see that we have two panels in place.
回到我们的网页，你可以看到这里有两个面板了
The first panel is open because we use the in class for
第一个面板是打开状态
that panel body there.
因为我们在 panel-body 里使用了 in 类
The second panel is closed at this moment, but if you click on the second panel,
第二个面板目前为关闭状态，但当你点击第二个面板
notice that the accordion behavior comes into action, here.
请注意这里将呈现手风琴效果
So you can click on the two leader's names,
所以，你可以点击这两个领导人的名字
and then you can see the accordion behavior coming into action here.
然后你就能在这看到手风琴效果了
Now, we're gonna complete this for the remaining two
现在，我们将实现这个列表中余下的两个领导人
leaders in this list here and then come back and look at the webpage.
然后再回头看看网页长什么样
After completing the changes, going back and looking at the webpage,
在完成这些修改后，回头看看现在的网页
we now see that the full corporate leaders information is now-
现在我们能看到所有公司领导人的信息在手风琴里
Inside an accordion, so you can click on any one of the leaders and
然后你可以单击任何一个领导人的名字
then you can see the accordion in action here.
这样就可以看到手风琴效果了
Our next step is to introduce the Scrollspy.
我们下一步将引入滚动监听 (Scrollspy)
So to do that, what we're going to first do is to move this entire
为了实现这个功能 我们将要把整个页面
content in this web page to the left and
的内容往左移
create some space on the right side so that we can introduce a Scrollspy there.
以便在右边创建空间 这样我们就能在这引入滚动监听
To do that, we will enclose this whole content inside a row and
要往左移 我们将把所有内容放到一个 row 里的
then give that a column class of ten columns so
一个带有 10 列的纵列类里
that we are left with two columns on the right side for the Scrollspy.
这样我们在右边就有 2 列宽度的空间用于滚动监听了
So let me make the change to the webpage, and
让我们去修改网页
then we'll come back and have a look at a change to this page.
然后再回头看看有什么变化
To create enough space on the website for the scrollspy,
为了给滚动监听创建足够的空间
I'm going to go into this container and then include its entire
我打算来到这个 container 类
content into another column there.
然后把整个内容包含到另一纵列里
So to do that, let me introduce the code here.
让我来加入以下代码
So here, I have introduced another row and
在这里我已经加入了另一个 row
introduced a column class with column xs-12 and sm-10.
并引入一个 class="col-xs-12 col-sm-10" 的纵列类
And then the entire content will be enclosed inside this ten columns here.
然后，整个内容都会放到这个 10 列的纵列类里
After making the changes, looking at the webpage now
在应用了所有修改后 让我们来看看页面
we notice that we have created enough space on the right side for
我们发现在右边已经创建了足够的空间
us to introduce a vertical navigation element there to use as a Scrollspy.
以便在这引入垂直导航元素 也就是滚动监听
To introduce the Scrollspy, I am going to go into the body and
要引入滚动监听 我打算到 body 里
introduce the data target and the data offset here.
引入 data-target 和 data-offset
So introducing these two elements there, so
所以 在这引入这两个属性
you can see that I have now modified the body to say the data-spy,
你会看到我现在已经修改了 body 并设置 data-spy="scroll"
scroll, and data-target, which is the ID of the Scrollspy that
以及 data-target，这是后面要引入的滚动监听的 ID
I'm gonna introduce later and the data-offset is 200 here.
我还在这设置了 data-offset="200"
To introduce a Scrollspy I come down the bottom of the page just before the footer.
要引入滚动监听 我来到页面的底部，在footer 之前
Inside the row of the container,
在 container 的 row 里面
I will introduce a nav element, which is going to act as my Scrollspy.
我会引入一个 nav 元素 也就是我们的滚动监听组件
Let me introduce the code there and then come back to explain it to you.
让我先添加好代码再回头跟你解释一下
So coming back here you see that I have now a nav class remember
回到这里，你看到我现在有一个 nav 标签
that the scroll spy works only when you use it on a nav element there.
请记住，滚动监听只有当你使用 nav 元素时才会工作
So here I have a nav class for which I have introduced the classes as
所以，我在这个 nav 标签的类里添加了 hidden-xs
hidden access, meaning that this nav element is going to be hidden
也就是说，这个 nav 元素将会隐藏
when I am viewing the webpage on an extra small screen.
如果我们在一个特小屏幕上查看网页的话
So I don't need the scroll spire on extra small screens.
我们不需要在特小屏幕上显示滚动监听
For small to large screens, this Scrollspy is going to occupy two columns.
而对于从小屏幕到大屏幕 这个滚动监听将占据两列空间
So recall that we just created two empty columns on the right side, so
回忆一下我们刚刚在右边创建了两列大小的空间
that is what I'm going to make use of for the Scrollspy.
我们将用于滚动监听组件
Now the Scrollspy itself is created using the ul class here, for
现滚动监听本身将在这使用 ul 类
which I am Using the nav-pills here, and the nav-stacked.
我在这使用了 nav-pills 和 nav-stacked
So this means that this is a sort of vertical pills that I am creating here.
也就意味着这是一个垂直的药片样式
Now, to this, I am also introducing this data-spy affix here.
在这，我还引入了 data-spy="affix"
So to turn that into an affix class there, and then the data off the top is 400.
来把它变为一个附加导航 (Affix) 类  然后 data-offset-top="400"
You have already seen how the affix works earlier.
你之前已经看到了附加导航是怎么工作的了
So with this introduction, the Scrollspy will be in place.
所以，这里会先对滚动监听进行说明
Now in order for the Scrollspy to work, recall that the links
要使滚动监听正常工作，回想一下这些链接
should be introduced to the elements.
需要引用到这些元素里
So in this web page, these should be introduced to
对于本页面来说
the rows of the content, here.
这些需要引入到页面内容中的行里
So let me go ahead and introduce the IDs for the three rows there.
让我现在就去引入这些 ID 到那三行中去
And then the last step is to modify our
而最后一步就是修改我们的 CSS 文件
CSS file to introduce the affects class there.
去添加 Affix 类进去
Going into the content rows for
来到页面内容的行里
that row containing the history I am going to introduce an ID as history.
对于那个包含历史信息的行，我们打算引入一个 ID 叫 history
The second row would be called with an ID of corporate.
第二行的 ID 将被称为 corporate
And the third row will have an ID of facts.
然后第三行的 ID 将是 facts
Let's save the file and then we will go into the mystylestarts CSS file and
让我们保存文件，然后到 mystyle.css 中去
introduce the affix CSS styles class there.
在那将添加 affix 的 CSS 样式类
In the my style starts CSS file we go to the bottom and
在 mystyle.css 文件中，我们来到最底部
then I will introduce the affix class here.
然后在这添加 affix 类
For this affix class, I am declaring the top to be 100 pixels, so
对于这个 affix 类，我定义了 top: 100px
this is how the affix works.
所以，affix 就是这样工作的
So, saving the changes, let's go back and look at our webpage.
然后保存这些修改，让我们回头看看我们的网页
Returning to our webpage, we now see that the Scrollspy
回到我们的网页，我们现在看到了滚动监听
is available on the right side and it is also
出现在页面的右侧
incorporated with the affix class in place.
并和附加导航共同工作
So as we scroll up, the nav moves upwards but at a certain
当我们往上滚动时，导航栏会往上移，但移到某一特定点时
point the Affix class takes over and then the nav gets fixed at that point.
附加导航 (Affix) 类起作用了 导航栏就会固定在这点上
You can also see the ScrollSpy in action,
你会看到滚动监听起作用
so as we scroll our page,
当你滚动我们的页面时
as the contents come up the nav reflects
随着内容不断往上移
the current content being viewed on the web page.
导航栏反映了页面中当前显示的内容
So you can now see this Scrollspy in action together with the affix plug in.
所以，现在你看到了滚动监听和附加导航是怎么一起工作的了
So as you see that as we scroll back the nav is moved out of the way.
当我们滚动回来后，你看到导航栏将不再固定了
This completes this exercise.
以上 我们完成了这次练习
So, in this exercise, we saw three things.
在这个练习里 我们看到了三样东西
We saw the use of the accordion with the collapse plug in that we have seen earlier
我们之前看到了怎么用折叠类来实现手风琴效果的
and we saw the use of the Scrollspy and Affix class.
我们还看到了滚动监听和附加导航的用法